Logan Thomas

Senior Associate Data Scientist I

Born 1989 in Mountain View, CA





Experience

Senior Associate Data Scientist I

Protection Engineering Consultants Austin, TX Aug 2019 - Present Advanced Technology & Research Team

Python Technical Curriculum Developer & Online Instructor

DataCamp Remote Feb 2019 - Present

Lead Data Scientist

Nielsen Austin, TX Oct 2018 - Aug 2019 Machine Learning & Algorithms Team

Senior Data Scientist

Nielsen San Francisco, CA Aug 2016 - Oct 2018 **Digital Product Team**

Applied Analytics Program Associate - School of **Professional Studies**

Columbia University Remote Sep 2016 - Dec 2016 Applied Analytics in an Organizational Context

Data Scientist

Nielsen Tampa, FL & San Francisco, CA July 2014 - Aug 2016 **Emerging Leaders Program**



Education

University of Florida

Master of Science in Mechanical Engineering 2012 - 2014

Minor in Statistics

Palm Beach Atlantic University

Bachelor of Science in Mathematics 2008 - 2012

Minor in Biblical Studies; Graduated Summa Cum Laude

Projects

turkey-bowl Python Thanksgiving tradition -Mock NFL fantasy football draft.

repo-scrape Python GitHub metadata scraping (Hacktoberfest).

python-practice Python Collection of personal Python notes, challenges, and scripts.



Contributions

pyjanitor Pythonic API for elegant Distributed Evolutionary data cleaning and method Algorithms in Python.

Python package to define. operate and manipulate

About me

I'm a highly motivated and naturally curious individual with 6 years of experience using data science & machine learning techniques. I exhibit an analytical and detail-oriented nature while placing strong value on building relationships.

Skills

| Python | Spark | S | QL | R | |
|----------|----------|------------|----|--------|------|
| NumPy | pandas | as sci | | kit-l€ | earn |
| PyTorch | Tenso | TensorFlow | | | |
| Security | Clearand | ce | | | |

Contact



✓ logan.thomas005@gmail.com

(321) 961-9107

in logan-thomas

loganthomas